{
    "subject": "resource/Mi_Fu",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Mi Fu (Chinese: \u7c73\u82be or \u7c73\u9efb; pinyin: M\u01d0 F\u00fa, 1051\u20131107) was a Chinese painter, poet, and calligrapher born in Taiyuan during the Song Dynasty. In painting he gained renown for his style of painting misty landscapes. This style would be deemed the \"Mi Fu\" style and involved the use of large wet dots of ink applied with a flat brush. His poetry followed the style of Li Bai and his calligraphy that of Wang Xizhi. His uninhibited style made him disliked at the Song court.He is best known for his calligraphy, and he was regarded as one of the four greatest calligraphers of the Song Dynasty.  His style arises from that of calligraphers in earlier dynasties, but with a unique mark of his own.As a personality Mi Fu was noted as an eccentric. At times they even deemed him \"Madman Mi\" because he was obsessed with collecting stones and even declared one stone to be his brother. Hence he would bow to his \"brother\" rock in a display of the filial devotion given to older brothers. He also was known as a heavy drinker. His son, Mi Youren, would also be a famous painter in his father's artistic style. Unlike his father Mi Youren lived to be quite elderly, dying at the age of 79.",
    "human_readable": "Mi Fu was a Chinese painter, poet, and calligrapher who was born in Taiyuan during the Song Dynasty.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8919185400009155,
            "question": "During which dynasty was Mi Fu born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7368763089179993,
            "question": "Name a period of Chinese history that Mi Fu lived through."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7141259908676147,
            "question": "Where was Mi Fu born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6668278574943542,
            "question": "What is the name of the dynasty associated with Mi Fu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5930600166320801,
            "question": "What was Mi Fu known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.477836549282074,
            "question": "Besides painting, what other art form was Mi Fu skilled in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4387572109699249,
            "question": "Can you describe some characteristics of Mi Fu's artistic style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40042844414711,
            "question": "Mi Fu is considered a prominent figure in which country's history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2971334159374237,
            "question": "What makes Mi Fu a significant historical figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22558918595314026,
            "question": "What three artistic disciplines did Mi Fu excel in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mi Fu was a Chinese painter, poet, and calligrapher who was born in Taiyuan during the Song Dynasty.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2073_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Mi Fu a significant historical figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2073_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mi Fu is considered a prominent figure in which country's history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2073_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe some characteristics of Mi Fu's artistic style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2073_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2073_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Mi Fu as a Chinese painter, poet, and calligrapher born in Taiyuan during the Song Dynasty. This supports the statement that Mi Fu was indeed a Chinese painter, poet, and calligrapher who was born in Taiyuan during the Song Dynasty."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}